<tv><program channel="1" start="20250404000000" stop="20250404020000"><title lang="en" id="tt0120764" duration="120">My Favorite Martian</title><desc lang="en">News producer Tim O'Hara gets himself fired for unwillingly compromising his bosses' daughter Brace Channing during a live transmission. A little later he witnesses the crashing of a small martian spacecraft realizing his one-time chance of delivering a story that will rock the earth. Since Tim took the original but scaled down spaceship with him the martian follows him to retrieve it.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama Family Science Fiction</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404020000" stop="20250404040000"><title lang="en" id="tt0303929" duration="120">Dracula III Legacy</title><desc lang="en">In the near future Uffizi and Luke travel to the remote reaches of war torn Romania to rescue Elizabeth and finish the vampire once and for all. Along the way they encounter TV news journalist and a corps of rebels trying to fight the vampire uprising which plagues their country.</desc><genres lang="en">Horror</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id14:  Horror Movies at Nights(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404040000" stop="20250404053000"><title lang="en" id="tt0100395" duration="90">Postcards from the Edge</title><desc lang="en">Substance-addicted Hollywood actress Suzanne Vale is on the skids. After a spell at a detox centre her film company insists as a condition of continuing to employ her that she live with her mother Doris Mann herself once a star and now a champion drinker. Such a set-up is bad news for Suzanne who has struggled for years to get out of her mother's shadow and who finds her mother still treats her like a child. Despite these problems - and further ones to do with the men in in her life - Suzanne can begin to see the funny side of her situation and it also starts to occur to her that not only do daughters have mothers mothers do too.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404053000" stop="20250404070000"><title lang="en" id="tt0071604" duration="90">Hearts and Minds</title><desc lang="en">This film recounts the history and attitudes of the opposing sides of the Vietnam War using archival news footage as well as their own film and interviews. A key theme is how attitudes of American racism and self-righteousness militarism helped create and prolong this bloody conflict. The film also endeaveors to give voice to the Vietnamese people themselves as to how the war has affected them and their reasons why they fight the United States and other western powers while showing the basic humanity of the people that US propaganda tried to dismiss.</desc><genres lang="en">Documentary War</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id10:  Old Classic Movies at Early Morning</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404070000" stop="20250404090000"><title lang="en" id="tt0092699" duration="120">Broadcast News</title><desc lang="en">Basket-case network news producer Jane Craig falls for new reporter Tom Grunnick a pretty boy who represents the trend towards entertainment news she despises. Aaron Altman a talented but plain correspondent carries an unrequited torch for Jane. Sparks fly between the three as the network prepares for big changes and both the news and Jane must decide between style and substance.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="1" start="20250404090000" stop="20250404103000"><title lang="en" id="tt1787777" duration="90">Page One Inside the New York Times</title><desc lang="en">Unprecedented access to the New York Times newsroom yields a complex view of the transformation of a media landscape fraught with both peril and opportunity.</desc><genres lang="en">Documentary</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="1" start="20250404103000" stop="20250404120000"><title lang="en" id="tt0392878" duration="90">The Onion Movie</title><desc lang="en">Venerable newscaster Norm Archer reports the latest news in politics health culture and entertainment - such as an automotive recall of decapitation-inducing "Neckbelts" and a study finding that "depression hits losers hardest". This compilation of bogus news stories celebrity profiles movie trailers and skits come courtesy of the ace satirists at The Onion.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404120000" stop="20250404140000"><title lang="en" id="tt0457936" duration="120">Hell</title><desc lang="en">No overview found.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404140000" stop="20250404160000"><title lang="en" id="tt1320297" duration="120">Si può fare</title><desc lang="en">No overview found.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404160000" stop="20250404180000"><title lang="en" id="tt0772193" duration="120">Primeval</title><desc lang="en">A news team is sent to Burundi to capture and bring home a legendary 25-foot crocodile. Their difficult task turns potentially deadly when a warlord targets them for death.</desc><genres lang="en">Adventure</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404180000" stop="20250404200000"><title lang="en" id="tt0408524" duration="120">Bad News Bears</title><desc lang="en">Morris Buttermaker is a burned-out minor league baseball player who loves to drink and can't keep his hands to himself. His long-suffering lawyer arranges for him to manage a local Little League team and Buttermaker soon finds himself the head of a rag-tag group of misfit players. Through unconventional team-building exercises and his offbeat coaching style Buttermaker helps his hapless Bears prepare to meet their rivals the Yankees.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Family</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id7:  Family with Comedy genre films at Afternoon or Evening</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404200000" stop="20250404220000"><title lang="en" id="tt0427528" duration="120">Mercenary for Justice</title><desc lang="en">Mercenary John Seeger is one of the best in the business. John and his crew battle some soldiers on Galmoral Island in Southern Africa as they're trying to rescue the French Ambassador -- there's a coup going on. Some of John's soldiers unload their machine guns into the Ambassador and his family blowing the mission and getting his best friend Radio Jones killed. He heads back to the US and visits Radio's wife Shondra to tells her the news and then promises that he'll take care of her and her son Eddie. But shortly after he makes that vow Shondra and Eddie get kidnapped.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id8:  Action Movies at Prime Time(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404220000" stop="20250405000000"><title lang="en" id="tt1787759" duration="120">Madea's Big Happy Family</title><desc lang="en">Shirley has important news for her family but she has five grown children with different lifestyles and finds it difficult to get them and the kids all together. So in steps Madea the Matriarch General to put the family's life in perspective with a hilarious twist on financial difficulties drugs and most important family secrets. The next generation has a lot to learn. In her own way Madea expresses how deliverance won't change you to be someone else but will allow you to be who you really are.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule), Rule - OM1:  Adult-rated Movies should not be scheduled consecutively</applied_rules></program></tv>