<tv date="20250404142830 +0530" generator_ENfo_name="epg.pw" generator_ENfo_url="https://epg.pw" source_ENfo_name="FREE EPG" source_ENfo_url="https://epg.pw/xmltv/epg_EN.xml"><channel id="1"><display-name lang="en">Cognizant News</display-name><icon src="https://example.com/Action_logo.png" /></channel><channel id="2"><display-name lang="en">Romance</display-name><icon src="https://example.com/Romance_logo.png" /></channel><channel id="3"><display-name lang="en">Thriller</display-name><icon src="https://example.com/Thriller_logo.png" /></channel><channel id="4"><display-name lang="en">Crime</display-name><icon src="https://example.com/Crime_logo.png" /></channel><program channel="1" start="20250404000000" stop="20250404013000"><title lang="en" id="tt0100395" duration="90">Postcards from the Edge</title><desc lang="en">Substance-addicted Hollywood actress Suzanne Vale is on the skids. After a spell at a detox centre her film company insists as a condition of continuing to employ her that she live with her mother Doris Mann herself once a star and now a champion drinker. Such a set-up is bad news for Suzanne who has struggled for years to get out of her mother's shadow and who finds her mother still treats her like a child. Despite these problems - and further ones to do with the men in in her life - Suzanne can begin to see the funny side of her situation and it also starts to occur to her that not only do daughters have mothers mothers do too.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404013000" stop="20250404033000"><title lang="en" id="tt0303929" duration="120">Dracula III Legacy</title><desc lang="en">In the near future Uffizi and Luke travel to the remote reaches of war torn Romania to rescue Elizabeth and finish the vampire once and for all. Along the way they encounter TV news journalist and a corps of rebels trying to fight the vampire uprising which plagues their country.</desc><genres lang="en">Horror</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id14:  Horror Movies at Nights(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404033000" stop="20250404053000"><title lang="en" id="tt0120764" duration="120">My Favorite Martian</title><desc lang="en">News producer Tim O'Hara gets himself fired for unwillingly compromising his bosses' daughter Brace Channing during a live transmission. A little later he witnesses the crashing of a small martian spacecraft realizing his one-time chance of delivering a story that will rock the earth. Since Tim took the original but scaled down spaceship with him the martian follows him to retrieve it.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama Family Science Fiction</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404053000" stop="20250404070000"><title lang="en" id="tt1787777" duration="90">Page One Inside the New York Times</title><desc lang="en">Unprecedented access to the New York Times newsroom yields a complex view of the transformation of a media landscape fraught with both peril and opportunity.</desc><genres lang="en">Documentary</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="1" start="20250404070000" stop="20250404083000"><title lang="en" id="tt0071604" duration="90">Hearts and Minds</title><desc lang="en">This film recounts the history and attitudes of the opposing sides of the Vietnam War using archival news footage as well as their own film and interviews. A key theme is how attitudes of American racism and self-righteousness militarism helped create and prolong this bloody conflict. The film also endeaveors to give voice to the Vietnamese people themselves as to how the war has affected them and their reasons why they fight the United States and other western powers while showing the basic humanity of the people that US propaganda tried to dismiss.</desc><genres lang="en">Documentary War</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id10:  Old Classic Movies at Early Morning</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404083000" stop="20250404103000"><title lang="en" id="tt0092699" duration="120">Broadcast News</title><desc lang="en">Basket-case network news producer Jane Craig falls for new reporter Tom Grunnick a pretty boy who represents the trend towards entertainment news she despises. Aaron Altman a talented but plain correspondent carries an unrequited torch for Jane. Sparks fly between the three as the network prepares for big changes and both the news and Jane must decide between style and substance.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="1" start="20250404103000" stop="20250404123000"><title lang="en" id="tt0457936" duration="120">Hell</title><desc lang="en">No overview found.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404123000" stop="20250404143000"><title lang="en" id="tt1320297" duration="120">Si può fare</title><desc lang="en">No overview found.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404143000" stop="20250404160000"><title lang="en" id="tt0392878" duration="90">The Onion Movie</title><desc lang="en">Venerable newscaster Norm Archer reports the latest news in politics health culture and entertainment - such as an automotive recall of decapitation-inducing "Neckbelts" and a study finding that "depression hits losers hardest". This compilation of bogus news stories celebrity profiles movie trailers and skits come courtesy of the ace satirists at The Onion.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404160000" stop="20250404180000"><title lang="en" id="tt0772193" duration="120">Primeval</title><desc lang="en">A news team is sent to Burundi to capture and bring home a legendary 25-foot crocodile. Their difficult task turns potentially deadly when a warlord targets them for death.</desc><genres lang="en">Adventure</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404180000" stop="20250404200000"><title lang="en" id="tt0408524" duration="120">Bad News Bears</title><desc lang="en">Morris Buttermaker is a burned-out minor league baseball player who loves to drink and can't keep his hands to himself. His long-suffering lawyer arranges for him to manage a local Little League team and Buttermaker soon finds himself the head of a rag-tag group of misfit players. Through unconventional team-building exercises and his offbeat coaching style Buttermaker helps his hapless Bears prepare to meet their rivals the Yankees.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Family</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id7:  Family with Comedy genre films at Afternoon or Evening</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404200000" stop="20250404220000"><title lang="en" id="tt0427528" duration="120">Mercenary for Justice</title><desc lang="en">Mercenary John Seeger is one of the best in the business. John and his crew battle some soldiers on Galmoral Island in Southern Africa as they're trying to rescue the French Ambassador -- there's a coup going on. Some of John's soldiers unload their machine guns into the Ambassador and his family blowing the mission and getting his best friend Radio Jones killed. He heads back to the US and visits Radio's wife Shondra to tells her the news and then promises that he'll take care of her and her son Eddie. But shortly after he makes that vow Shondra and Eddie get kidnapped.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id8:  Action Movies at Prime Time(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="1" start="20250404220000" stop="20250405000000"><title lang="en" id="tt1787759" duration="120">Madea's Big Happy Family</title><desc lang="en">Shirley has important news for her family but she has five grown children with different lifestyles and finds it difficult to get them and the kids all together. So in steps Madea the Matriarch General to put the family's life in perspective with a hilarious twist on financial difficulties drugs and most important family secrets. The next generation has a lot to learn. In her own way Madea expresses how deliverance won't change you to be someone else but will allow you to be who you really are.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule), Rule - OM1:  Adult-rated Movies should not be scheduled consecutively</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404000000" stop="20250404013000"><title lang="en" id="tt0103855" duration="90">The Bodyguard</title><desc lang="en">A former Secret Service agent grudgingly takes an assignment to protect a pop idol who's threatened by a crazed fan. At first the safety-obsessed bodyguard and the self-indulgent diva totally clash. But before long all that tension sparks fireworks of another sort and the love-averse tough guy is torn between duty and romance.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller Action Drama Music Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404013000" stop="20250404030000"><title lang="en" id="tt0076095" duration="90">The Goodbye Girl</title><desc lang="en">Paula McFadden knows: In romance actors all follow the same stage instruction: Exit. Without warning her actor boyfriend split today for a movie role and sublet their Manhattan apartment. The new tenant's name: Elliot Garfield. Profession: actor. Richard Dreyfuss and Marsha Mason deliver comedy zingy repartee and bitter-to-best romance in The Goodbye Girl.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id9:  Old Movies at LateNights</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404030000" stop="20250404043000"><title lang="en" id="tt0054698" duration="90">Breakfast at Tiffany's</title><desc lang="en">Fortune hunter Holly Golightly finds herself captivated by aspiring writer Paul Varjak who's moved into her building on a wealthy woman's dime. As romance blooms between Paul and Holly Doc Golightly shows up on the scene revealing Holly's past.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Drama Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id9:  Old Movies at LateNights</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404043000" stop="20250404060000"><title lang="en" id="tt1493842" duration="90">Beauty &amp; the Briefcase</title><desc lang="en">A freelance writer looking for romance sells a story to Cosmopolitan magazine about finding love in the workplace and goes undercover at a Finance Company.</desc><genres lang="en">Romance Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="2" start="20250404060000" stop="20250404073000"><title lang="en" id="tt2094064" duration="90">Much Ado About Nothing</title><desc lang="en">A modern retelling of Shakespeare's classic comedy about two pairs of lovers with different takes on romance and a way with words.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="2" start="20250404073000" stop="20250404090000"><title lang="en" id="tt0162973" duration="90">Get Real</title><desc lang="en">A tenderly romantic coming-of-age story as two boys in a British school fall in love.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="2" start="20250404090000" stop="20250404110000"><title lang="en" id="tt1826590" duration="120">About Last Night</title><desc lang="en">A modern reimagining of the classic romantic comedy this contemporary version closely follows new love for two couples as they journey from the bar to the bedroom and are eventually put to the test in the real world.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="2" start="20250404110000" stop="20250404123000"><title lang="en" id="tt0332280" duration="90">The Notebook</title><desc lang="en">An epic love story centered around an older man who reads aloud to a woman with Alzheimer's. From a faded notebook the old man's words bring to life the story about a couple who is separated by World War II and is then passionately reunited seven years later after they have taken different paths.</desc><genres lang="en">Romance Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404123000" stop="20250404140000"><title lang="en" id="tt0368222" duration="90">Romance &amp; Cigarettes</title><desc lang="en">Down-and-dirty musical love story set in the world of the working class. Nick is an ironworker who builds and repairs bridges. He's married to Kitty a dressmaker a strong and gentle woman with whom he has three daughters. He is carrying on a torrid affair with a redheaded woman named Tula. Nick is basically a good hardworking man driven forward by will and blinded by his urges.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Music Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404140000" stop="20250404160000"><title lang="en" id="tt0423455" duration="120">Hemingway &amp; Gellhorn</title><desc lang="en">Writer Ernest Hemingway begins a romance with fellow scribe Martha Gellhorn.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404160000" stop="20250404180000"><title lang="en" id="tt0345061" duration="120">Code 46</title><desc lang="en">A futuristic 'Brief Encounter' a love story in which the romance is doomed by genetic incompatibility.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Romance Science Fiction Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404180000" stop="20250404193000"><title lang="en" id="tt0272360" duration="90">Winning London</title><desc lang="en">When Chloe and Riley Lawrence are invited to London to participate in the international Model U.N. competition they enjoy seeing the sights and head over heals romance with cute british boys of course.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Family</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id7:  Family with Comedy genre films at Afternoon or Evening</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404193000" stop="20250404213000"><title lang="en" id="tt1837562" duration="120">A Royal Night Out</title><desc lang="en">The film portrays a fairy tale re-imagining of V.E. Day in 1945 when Princess Elizabeth and her sister Margaret were allowed out from Buckingham Palace for the night to join in the celebrations where they encountered romance and danger.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller Romance Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id2:  Family Audience Movies at Prime Time</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404213000" stop="20250404233000"><title lang="en" id="tt0358135" duration="120">Shall We Dance?</title><desc lang="en">A romantic comedy where a bored overworked Estate Lawyer upon first sight of a beautiful instructor signs up for ballroom dancing lessons.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Romance Comedy</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id2:  Family Audience Movies at Prime Time</applied_rules></program><program channel="2" start="20250404233000" stop="20250405010000"><title lang="en" id="tt0102395" duration="90">Mannequin Two On the Move</title><desc lang="en">Although Jason works as a department store clerk he is also a reincarnated prince. Long ago his beloved Jessie was snatched away from him by an evil wizard who used his powers to transform her into wooden statue. Now Jessie is in Jason's department store as a mannequin. When he encounters her she awakens from her thousand-year sleep. They quickly revive their romance but the evil wizard has been reincarnated as well and he's up to no good.</desc><genres lang="en">Fantasy Comedy Science Fiction Romance</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule), Rule - OM1:  Adult-rated Movies should not be scheduled consecutively</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404000000" stop="20250404020000"><title lang="en" id="tt1650535" duration="120">The Entitled</title><desc lang="en">Without the security of the job he wants or the future he dreamed of Paul Dynan (Kevin Zegers) plans the perfect crime to help his struggling family - extort a fortune from three wealthy men (Ray Liotta Victor Garber Stephen McHattie. The plan to abduct their socialite children (Laura Vandervoort Dustin Milligan John Bregar) and a collect a healthy ransom of 3-million dollars. Over the course of one long night Paul and his accomplices hold the rich kids hostage awaiting the 3-million ransom with little idea of the secrets that will surface between the fathers when they are forced to choose between their children and their money. Once blood is shed and things go horribly wrong Paul must fight to stay one step ahead of his own twisted game.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404020000" stop="20250404040000"><title lang="en" id="tt0082951" duration="120">The Prowler</title><desc lang="en">A masked killer wearing World War II U.S. Army fatigues stalks a small New Jersey town bent on reliving a 35-year-old double murder by focusing on a group of college kids holding an annual Spring Dance.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller Horror Mystery</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id9:  Old Movies at LateNights</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404040000" stop="20250404053000"><title lang="en" id="tt1369706" duration="90">The Ward</title><desc lang="en">A thriller centered on an institutionalized young woman who becomes terrorized by a ghost.</desc><genres lang="en">Horror Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="3" start="20250404053000" stop="20250404073000"><title lang="en" id="tt1707392" duration="120">Lovely Molly</title><desc lang="en">A horror/thriller centered on one troubled young woman and the evil power that exists inside of her.</desc><genres lang="en">Horror Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="3" start="20250404073000" stop="20250404090000"><title lang="en" id="tt1976000" duration="90">The Two Faces of January</title><desc lang="en">A thriller centered on a con artist his wife and a stranger who try to flee a foreign country after one of them is caught up in the murder of a private detective.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="3" start="20250404090000" stop="20250404110000"><title lang="en" id="tt0848552" duration="120">The Mad</title><desc lang="en">A horror-thriller in which a doctor and his teenage daughter are terrorized by flesh-eating zombies at a truck stop.</desc><genres lang="en">Comedy Horror Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="3" start="20250404110000" stop="20250404123000"><title lang="en" id="tt1667310" duration="90">Deadfall</title><desc lang="en">A thriller that follows two siblings who decide to fend for themselves in the wake of a botched casino heist and their unlikely reunion during another family's Thanksgiving celebration.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Drama Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404123000" stop="20250404140000"><title lang="en" id="tt1615147" duration="90">Margin Call</title><desc lang="en">A thriller that revolves around the key people at an investment bank over a 24-hour period during the early stages of the financial crisis.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404140000" stop="20250404153000"><title lang="en" id="tt2992524" duration="90">The Guvnors</title><desc lang="en">The Guvnors is a violent thriller set amongst the clans and firms of South East London bringing two generations together in brutal conflict.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404153000" stop="20250404173000"><title lang="en" id="tt0497323" duration="120">Anamorph</title><desc lang="en">A psychological thriller based on the concept of anamorphosis a painting technique that manipulates the laws of perspective to create two competing images on a single canvas.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404173000" stop="20250404190000"><title lang="en" id="tt1580426" duration="90">Repeaters</title><desc lang="en">A gritty mind-bending thriller about three twenty-somethings who find themselves in an impossible time labyrinth where each day they awaken to the same terrifying day as the preceding one.</desc><genres lang="en">Science Fiction Thriller Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="3" start="20250404190000" stop="20250404203000"><title lang="en" id="tt0881320" duration="90">Sanctum</title><desc lang="en">The 3-D action-thriller Sanctum from executive producer James Cameron follows a team of underwater cave divers on a treacherous expedition to the largest most beautiful and least accessible cave system on Earth. When a tropical storm forces them deep into the caverns they must fight raging water deadly terrain and creeping panic as they search for an unknown escape route to the sea. Master diver Frank McGuire (Richard Roxburgh) has explored the South Pacific's Esa-ala Caves for months. But when his exit is cut off in a flash flood Frank's team--including 17-year-old son Josh (Rhys Wakefield) and financier Carl Hurley (Ioan Gruffudd)--are forced to radically alter plans. With dwindling supplies the crew must navigate an underwater labyrinth to make it out. Soon they are confronted with the unavoidable question: Can they survive or will they be trapped forever?</desc><genres lang="en">Action Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id8:  Action Movies at Prime Time(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404203000" stop="20250404223000"><title lang="en" id="tt0098141" duration="120">The Punisher</title><desc lang="en">The avenging angel of Marvel Comics fame comes brilliantly to life in this searing action-adventure thriller Dolph Lundgren stars as Frank Castle a veteran cop who loses his entire family to a mafia car bomb. Only his ex-partner believes Castle survived the blast to become THE PUNISHER ... a shadowy invincible fighter against evil who lives for total revenge on his mob enemies.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id8:  Action Movies at Prime Time(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="3" start="20250404223000" stop="20250405003000"><title lang="en" id="tt1867093" duration="120">The Samaritan</title><desc lang="en">After twenty years in prison Foley is finished with the grifter's life. When he meets an elusive young woman named Iris the possibility of a new start looks real. But his past is proving to be a stubborn companion.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule), Rule - OM1:  Adult-rated Movies should not be scheduled consecutively</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404000000" stop="20250404013000"><title lang="en" id="tt0090735" duration="90">Black Moon Rising</title><desc lang="en">An FBI free-lancer stashes a stolen Las Vegas-crime tape in a high-tech car stolen by someone else.</desc><genres lang="en">Science Fiction Action Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">R</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule)</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404013000" stop="20250404030000"><title lang="en" id="tt0086356" duration="90">The Star Chamber</title><desc lang="en">Disgusted with criminals escaping the judicial system via technicalities an idealistic young judge investigates an alternative method for punishing the guilty.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Crime Drama Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id9:  Old Movies at LateNights</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404030000" stop="20250404050000"><title lang="en" id="tt0068646" duration="120">The Godfather</title><desc lang="en">Spanning the years 1945 to 1955 a chronicle of the fictional Italian-American Corleone crime family. When organized crime family patriarch Vito Corleone barely survives an attempt on his life his youngest son Michael steps in to take care of the would-be killers launching a campaign of bloody revenge.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Crime</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id9:  Old Movies at LateNights</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404050000" stop="20250404063000"><title lang="en" id="tt0096257" duration="90">The Thin Blue Line</title><desc lang="en">Errol Morris's unique documentary dramatically re-enacts the crime scene and investigation of a police officer's murder in Dallas.</desc><genres lang="en">Mystery Documentary Crime</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id10:  Old Classic Movies at Early Morning</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404063000" stop="20250404083000"><title lang="en" id="tt0071562" duration="120">The Godfather Part II</title><desc lang="en">In the continuing saga of the Corleone crime family a young Vito Corleone grows up in Sicily and in 1910s New York. In the 1950s Michael Corleone attempts to expand the family business into Las Vegas Hollywood and Cuba.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Crime</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id10:  Old Classic Movies at Early Morning</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404083000" stop="20250404100000"><title lang="en" id="tt2101341" duration="90">Dead Man Down</title><desc lang="en">In New York City a crime lord's right-hand man is seduced by a woman seeking retribution.</desc><genres lang="en">Thriller Action Crime Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="4" start="20250404100000" stop="20250404113000"><title lang="en" id="tt1220888" duration="90">Henry's Crime</title><desc lang="en">An aimless man is sent to prison for a crime he did not commit.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Comedy Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="4" start="20250404113000" stop="20250404130000"><title lang="en" id="tt0139668" duration="90">True Crime</title><desc lang="en">Clint Eastwood plays Steve Everett a journalist recovering from alcoholism given the task of covering the execution of murderer Frank Beechum (played by Isaiah Washington). Everett discovers that Beechum might be innocent but has only a few hours to prove his theory and save Beechum's life.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404130000" stop="20250404143000"><title lang="en" id="tt1258120" duration="90">L'Armée du crime</title><desc lang="en">This gripping historical drama recounts the story of Armenian-born Missak Manouchian (Simon Abkarian) a woodworker and political activist who led an immigrant laborer division of the Parisian Resistance on 30 operations against the Nazis in 1943. The Nazis branded the group an Army of Crime an anti-immigrant propaganda stunt that backfired as the team's members became martyrs for the Resistance. Virginie Ledoyen co-stars as Manouchian's wife.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Foreign History</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404143000" stop="20250404160000"><title lang="en" id="tt2925642" duration="90">Kids for Cash</title><desc lang="en">A look into the judicial scandal that rocked the nation.</desc><genres lang="en">Documentary Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">G</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404160000" stop="20250404173000"><title lang="en" id="tt0802948" duration="90">An American Crime</title><desc lang="en">The true story of suburban housewife Gertrude Baniszewski who kept a teenage girl locked in the basement of her Indiana home during the 1960s.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id5:  Moderately Rated Films at Late Morning or AfterNoon</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404173000" stop="20250404190000"><title lang="en" id="tt0099409" duration="90">Desperate Hours</title><desc lang="en">A criminal holds a wealthy family hostage.</desc><genres lang="en">Mystery Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG-13</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>0</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en" /></program><program channel="4" start="20250404190000" stop="20250404203000"><title lang="en" id="tt0087507" duration="90">Johnny Dangerously</title><desc lang="en">Set in the 1930s an honest goodhearted man is forced to turn to a life of crime to finance his neurotic mother's skyrocketing medical bills.</desc><genres lang="en">Action Comedy Thriller Crime</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id2:  Family Audience Movies at Prime Time</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404203000" stop="20250404220000"><title lang="en" id="tt0090670" duration="90">At Close Range</title><desc lang="en">Based upon the true story of Bruce Johnston Sr. his son and his brothers together they constituted one of suburban Philadelphia's most notorious crime families during the 1970's. Their criminal activities ranged from burglary theft... and ultimately murder.</desc><genres lang="en">Crime Drama</genres><pc_rating lang="en">PG</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>10</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id2:  Family Audience Movies at Prime Time</applied_rules></program><program channel="4" start="20250404220000" stop="20250405000000"><title lang="en" id="tt0117107" duration="120">Mulholland Falls</title><desc lang="en">In 1950s Los Angeles a special crime squad of the LAPD investigates the murder of a young woman.</desc><genres lang="en">Drama Mystery Thriller</genres><pc_rating lang="en">NC-17</pc_rating><ad_slate_length>20</ad_slate_length><applied_rules lang="en">Rule - Id1:  Adult Rated Movies at Late Night(strict rule), Rule - OM1:  Adult-rated Movies should not be scheduled consecutively</applied_rules></program></tv>